Guide to the John Anthony Danaher Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- GENERAL FILES, 1916-1979; Series III; 6 linear feet (16 boxes)
  - Scrapbooks
    - 1928-1936 (Box 73, Folder 842)
    - 1948 (Box 74, Folder 842)
- Additional material, 1900-1982; Accession 2015-M-063
  - Clippings, 1900-1976 (Box 1, Folder 1-11, Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence
    - General, 1940-1982 (Box 1, Folder 12-16)
    - Clifford, J. Garry, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Danaher Jr., Cornelius J., 1944-1945 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Danaher Sr., Cornelius J., 1940-1961 (Box 2, Folder 1-2)
    - Danaher, Francis R., 1942-1980 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Danaher, Lawrence, 1940-1942 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Danaher, Letitia, 1942-1954 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Judgeship, 1953 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Kammerman, David, 1980-1982 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Letters of introduction, 1938 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Manuscripts and transcripts, 1938-1983, undated (Box 2, Folder 9-15)
  - Photographs, 1930-1944, undated (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Programs and tributes, 1920-1953 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Scrapbook, 1939-11 (Box 4, Folder 1-2)
  - Subject files, 1921-1968 (Box 2, Folder 18-19)
- Additional material, 1920-1976; Accession 2015-M-064
  - Scrapbooks
    - 1935-1970 (Box 1, Folder 1-2)
    - 1920-1976 (Box 2, Folder 1-2)
    - 1935-1939 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - 1939 (Box 3, Folder 2-3)